Contact

sstatonrn@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/sarastaton-82aa54a (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

ACLS

BLS

Critical Care

Certifications

CEN

CPEN

Sara Staton

MSN, RN, CPEN, CEN

Conroe, Texas

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Emergency Nursing, Nursing Management, Patient Advocacy, Medical-Surgical, and Pediatrics. Strong healthcare services professional with a Masters degree focused in Administration from The University of Texas at Arlington.

Experience

CHI St. Luke's Health

3 years 9 months

Director Of Emergency Services

October 2019 - Present (8 months)

The Vintage Hospital

Manager Emergency Department September 2016 - Present (3 years 9 months)

CHI St. Luke's

RN

March 2015 - Present (5 years 3 months)

CHI St. Luke's

Americas ER

Director of Nursing

December 2013 - January 2015 (1 year 2 months)

PhysiciansER

Nurse Manager

September 2012 - December 2013 (1 year 4 months)

4019 I-45 North Conroe, Texas 77304

Kingwood Medical Center Hospital

RN

2010 - 2012 (2 years)

Kingwood Texas

St. Lukes the Woodlands Hospital RN

2006 - 2011 (5 years)

The Woodlands, Texas

St. Lukes Hospital the Woodlands PCA II 2006 - 2009 (3 years)

Education

The University of Texas at Arlington MSN, Administration · (2016 - 2018)

The University of Texas at Arlington
Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2016)

Lone Star College
Associate's Degree of Applied Science-Nursing, Sciences · (2002 - 2009)

The University of Texas at Arlington Nursing Science (2013)